A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Rockefeller University Press, Exhibits and Conferences FA958
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Rockefeller University Press, Exhibits and Conferences
1963-1976
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University Press
Rockefeller University
FA958
0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box.
1 box.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Material received from RU Press, June 1982.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 580
Scope and Contents
Documents exhibits and conferences, 1960s-1970s.
Medical research; Medical education; Medical sciences; Life sciences; Science -- Study and teaching; Cell and biomolecular sciences; Medicine, Preventive; Medical technology; Biology -- Research
- Arts and Crafts Exhibit, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Includes photographs.
- Arts and Crafts Exhibit, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Botanical Exhibit, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Minoru Niizuma Sculpture Exhibit (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Avery Memorial Gateway (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Dubos, R.J. Book proposal: Biology and Urban Life, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- "Beyond Tomorrow" Conference, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Peyton Rous Memorial Booklet (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
- National Academy of Sciences Centennial, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Press Book. The Richard Prentice Ettinger Program for Creative Writing. Symposium and Dinner. The Rockefeller Institute, 1963 October 29 (Box 1, Folder 12)